有没有人出7万?
Do I have 70?
7万.7万五
Seventy.Seventy-five.
8万
Eighty.
8万5
Eighty-five.
9万
Ninety.
9万5
Ninety-five.
10万
One hundred.
Leonard Wright画于1934的作品
Drawn in 1934 by Leonard Wright.
黑色风暴第一版原作的封面
The original artwork for the cover of Black Storm,Issue One.
出价十万镑
At 100,000.
有没有更高的?
Any more bids?
11万
One-ten.
11万镑?
At 110,000.
一次,两次
Going once,going twice.
成交
Sold.
不敢相信,我们做到了
I can't believe we just did that.
嘿,Eddie
Hello,Eddie.
再给我点时间
I need more time.
- 时间到了,我要拿回我的一万块 - 我现在没钱
- Time's up,I want my 10,000. - I haven't got it.
都怪那群该死的骗子 他们不肯付钱
It's these bloody grifters,they don't pay for anything.
那你就不该让他们在你酒吧里面赌,不是么?
Then you shouldn't let them gamble in your bar,should you?
我的意思是,我是个警察 我必须上报这件事
I mean,I am a police officer.I've got to report it.
- 你将失去你的执照 - 你不能这么做
- You're gonna lose your license. - But you can't.
这个地方是我所有的全部了
This place is all I've got.
你从没蹲过监狱吧,Eddie?
You ever been to prison,Eddie?
那是什么?
What's that?
这是要你在前台收银的抽屉 里解决的假钞
That's counterfeit money you've been laundering through your till.
求你了
Please.
告诉你,要我帮你,也得给我个名头 我要得是大鱼
I tell you what,I will settle for some names.I want the big fish.
不,不行.我不会告密的
No.No way.I am not a grass.
回答错误,Eddie
Wrong answer,Eddie.
好的,好的!
Okay!
有伙人常在这里喝东西 他们很善于干这个
There's this crew that drink in here,they play the long con.
名字
Names.
Mickey Bricks
Mickey Bricks.
本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子  字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir  Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第2季第4集
S02E04 Missions
也许我在这儿漏了点儿什么
Maybe I am missing something here.
只是,我觉得我们不是骗子么
Only,I thought we were grifters.
- 我的意思是,我不可能偷了这个的呀 - 那又怎么样?
- I mean we could've lifted this. - And then what?
我不知道,干好我们的本份,不是嘛?
I don't know.Do our thing,don't we?
创造奇迹
Work the magic.
说得好,Danny
Great plan,Danny.
我们干活的资金不够了 我们要搞点现金
It's wiped out our working capital.We will have to raise some cash.
把它当作一项投资
Think of it as an investment.
黑色风暴曾是个超级英雄,而这个
Black Storm was one of the original superheroes,and this...
就如同连环画界的蒙娜丽莎
is the Mona Lisa of comic book artwork.
这就是我们为什么要付11万镑的原因
That's why we had to pay ?10,000 for it.
他们说你要绞尽脑汁来存钱
They say you have to speculate to accumulate.
不对,你知道,这不对劲
No,you know,it feels all wrong.
我们应该为我们自己而感到自豪
We should be really proud of ourselves.
终于有这么一次 我们不用犯法了
For once,we did not break the law.
Ash,拍卖所的平面图看起来怎么样?
Ash,how are the auction house blueprints looking?
不简单,不过可以搞定
It won't be easy,but it's definitely doable.
是的,我们距离拍卖还有两周时间
Right,we've got two weeks until the next auction.
同时,我们要去搞点活动资金
Meantime,we'll need to raise some working capital.
但这个美妙之处在于 我们的人马可以推迟现金的流动
But the beauty of it is,our guy can delay the currency movement...
以便我们能够部好局
just long enough for us to place a spread bet.
我们就净赚百分之三百四百的利润了 轻而易举
We've been clearing 300,400% profit,easy.
太棒了!
Wow!
- 这太美妙了 - 美妙是美妙,但是是违法的
- That's beautiful. - That's beautiful,but illegal.
- 但是万无一失? - 完全没问题
- But foolproof? - Completely.
算我一份,当然,我们一块干
I'm in.Definitely.Let's do it.
没错
Right.
你做不做傻瓜?这是2万5千镑
You'd have to be an idiot not to.?5,000.
谢谢
Thank you.
让我们看看我们有多少了
Let's see what we've got here.
哦,谢谢
Yeah.Thank you.
生活所迫啊
Beats working for a living.
有事吗?
Can I help you?
我以诈骗罪逮捕你们
I am arresting you for fraud.
你们可以保持沉默
You don't have to say anything...
Danny当你对所问的不说话将会
but it may harm your defense if you do not mention when questioned...
成为你日后的成堂证供
something which you later rely on in court.
我们可以现在就开始
You can go for now.
我会联系你的,来做笔录的
I will contact you,take a statement.
转过来
Turn around.
好了,我们做个交易
Okay,here's the deal.
要么你们两个去监狱 要么我带着钱
You two can go to prison,or I can walk out of here...
从这里走出去,然后我们 当作什么也没发生过
with the money and we all forget this ever happened.
两面派警察
A bent copper.
- 这就是所谓的"保护公民,服务社会" - 真聪明
- So much for "Protect and Serve." - Brilliant.
你认为我们会让你
You think for one second that we are going to let you...
从这里大摇大摆走出去,还带着2万5千镑?
swan out of here with ?5,000?
想得美,小妞
You're dreaming,missy.
恐怕这正是你们所要做的
I think that's exactly what you're going to do...
除非Mickey现在有更好的主意
unless Mickey here fancies another spell inside.
还没有
Not particularly.
嘿,像你这样的人 让警察有了个坏名声
People like you,yeah,they give the police a very bad name.
我接受,那我们来谈谈吧,就现在,好吧
I take it we have a deal.Now,okay.
一干蠢事,他就来作证 而你们俩,就进监狱
Do anything stupid,he testifies,you two go to prison.
明白了没有?
Got it?
你明白他们所说的,该来的躲不掉
You know what they say,what goes around comes around.
那如果我是你的话 我现在就会很担心的
Then I'd be seriously worried,if I were you.
- 你们的? - 是的,我喜欢画画
- Yours? - Yeah,I like to draw.
- 你很了不起么? - 我的美术老师也这么说
- You are very good,aren't you? - That's what my art teacher said.
现在,一伙骗子
Now,what would a couple of grifters be doing...
要价值10万英镑的艺术品干吗
with artwork worth 100,000?
正如目录上所说 我们要对它进行拍卖
Like the catalogue says,we're auctioning it.
是的,我是说这个完全合法 我们有收据和一切证明
Yeah,I mean it's completely legit.We got receipts,we got everything.
她想干吗?
What's she doing?
你要干吗?
What are you doing?
基本上,你有5秒钟的时间
Basically you've got five seconds
来告诉我你们的计划,要么我就点着了它
to tell me the score or I torch it.
告诉你吧,没有什么计划
We told you.There's no score.
是的,我们只是在拍卖一些艺术作品
Yeah,we're auctioning some artwork.
没有法律说这个不行
No law against it.
- 没有什么计划 - 你敢
- There's no score. - You wouldn't dare.
好吧好吧!我们告诉你!快灭了它!
All right!We will tell you!Put it out!
现在,我要你一五一十老实交代
Now,you tell me everything...
这次,可不仅仅只是一块啤酒垫子
or this time,it won't be a beer mat.
我们打算今天下午拍卖这件艺术品
We're auctioning the artwork this afternoon.
我们需要一个真品 因为拍卖行会进行鉴定
We needed a genuine piece because the auction house like to authenticate...
艺术品,然后才会卖了它
the artwork before they sell it.
当它在台上展示的时候
While it's on display at the viewing...
我们就用赝品把真品换了
we switch the authentic artwork for a forgery.
真正拍卖掉的是赝品
It's the forgery that gets auctioned.
然后在另一方面
And then on the side...
我们把它卖给对头的收藏家
we sell the authentic artwork to a rival collector.
是的,我们说明白了吧?10万美元的利润?
Yeah,and we clear 100,000 profit.
你明白了没有?5万英镑的利润 我拿另外的5万
You clear 50,000 profit.I get the other 50.
5万英镑?
Fifty?
打个电话到拍卖所 你一毛钱不用出
One phone call to the auction house,you don't make a penny.
现在,我们要2万5来付赝品
Now,we need the 25,000 to pay the forger.
很公平
Fair enough.
放心,拍卖结束后 我们会跟你碰头的
Don't worry,we will meet you back here after the auction.
你知道吗?我想我会尾随其后的
You know what?I think I will tag along for the ride.
一个条件
One condition.
一旦你拿到钱 告诉我们,谁出卖了我们
Once you get your money,tell us who sold us out.
你凭什么认为有人出卖了你们?
What makes you think someone sold you out?
那么,去哪里?
So,where to?
我们要去拿赝品
We need to pick up the forgery.
再见,Eddie
Bye,Eddie.
- 一切还好吧,Mick? - 好得不得了
- Everything all right,Mick? - Absolutely fantastic.
这下好了,你说我们现在怎么办?告诉其他人吗?
This is great.What do you think we should do?Tell the others?
不,他们有事情要做,所以...
No,they've got their jobs to do.So...
没人告诉你们窃窃私语很不礼貌?
Did anyone ever tell you it's rude to whisper?
- 你觉得她身材怎么样? - 别
- Do you think she's fit? - Don't...
- 怎么了? - 想也别想
- What? - ...even think about it.
你知道,你能不能 你知道,如果你能
You know,would you have a few,you know,if you could?
什么叫我能不能?
What do you mean,if I could?
- 你干什么? - 你想怎样?
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
- Danny,你坐后面 - 你坐后面
- Danny,get in the back. - You get in the back.
不,我不坐后面
No,I am not getting in the back.
有什么问题吗?
Is there a problem?
我们在最后时刻要出价高过这 两个收藏家,他们可不想再输了
The two collectors we outbid at the last auction won't want to lose out again.
他们拍得越高 我们赚得越多
The higher they bid,the more profit we make.
- 稍稍的鼓励就可以了 - 完全正确
- A little encouragement goes a long way. - Absolutely.
你有什么建议?
You have any preference?
我选这个怪人
I'll take the geek.
温柔点
Be gentle.
就像一只小猫
As a kitten.
早上好,房东的煤气安全检查 我需要检查一下煤气设施
Morning.Landlord's gas safety checks.I need to inspect the gas appliances.
现在不太合适 我要上班
It's actually not a very good time.I've got to leave for work.
嘿,你看,这是你的事
Well,that's your problem,you see.
你天天早出晚归,而你却能够得到 煤气的安全检查
You're out all day,you get a buildup of gas from a faulty appliance.
你一回来,轻轻一按开关,!
You come home,flick on a light switch,bang!
还有件事情你要知道 他们会让你脑浆流一地的
Next thing you know,they are scraping your brains off the pavement.
好了,让我们先来检查看看炉子
Right.Let's start with the cooker.
是用电的
It's electric.
- 烧水壶? - 这里面
- Boiler? - In there.
好吧,在我检查的时候 我要你把热帽打开
Okay,I need you to turn the hot tap on in the bathroom while I check it.
太可惜了
Sad.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我喜欢超人
I love Superman.
虽然,我一直更喜欢作为普通人的Clark Kent,你知道
Although,I've always preferred him more as Clark Kent,you know.
强壮,但是显得脆弱,你知道
Strong,but vulnerable,you know...
那些眼镜
those glasses.
我的小侄子,他也很为他着迷
My little nephew,he's crazy about him as well.
事实上,我想买份礼物给他
Actually,I wanted to get him a present.
如果你不太忙的话,能帮我找些吗
Could you help me find some other stuff,if you are not too busy?
不,我的意思是,可以,我来帮你 不,我一点儿不忙
No,I mean,yes,I can help you.No,I'm not too busy.
我叫Neil
I'm Neil.
这是我的店
It's my shop.
你怎么看?
What do you know about that?
不好意思
Excuse me.
什么?
Yeah?
我无意中看到你的拍卖目录 是snap
I couldn't help noticing your auction catalogue.Snap.
你肯定是为流行艺术展而来吧
You must be here for the pop-art exhibition.
是的,我是Lichtenstein的超级粉丝
Yeah,I am a sucker for Lichtenstein.
- 你是收藏家吗? - 我被认为是在浪费时间
- Are you a collector? - I've been known to dabble.
或许你能够为我解释一些问题
Perhaps you could clear something up for me.
你对于
What do you make of the idea...
Lichtenstein在他的作品中 嘲笑自己的主题这个说法,怎么看?
that Lichtenstein is mocking his subjects in his paintings?
一个很普遍的误解.我能做过来吗?
A common misconception.May I?
哦,当然,请坐
Please,yes,of course.
Lichtenstein的连环画所 展示的是一个成年人
What Lichtenstein's comic book paintings show is a grown man finding...
在他所应该抛弃的垃圾中 寻到了生活意义
meaning in junk he's supposed to have thrown away.
这是关于能力和成年人梦幻的故事
They are about the energy of adolescent fantasy.
是的
Yes.
那么,为什么是连环画?
So,why comic books?
Mickey还是孩子的时候就迷上了他们
Mickey was into them when he was a kid.
因为传统艺术世界有太多的保安
Because there's too much security in the traditional art world.
他就是那种有点作的孩子 你知道,一天到晚哭
He was one of those specky kids.You know,a lot of crying.
- 请不要欺侮我 - 而且,这件艺术品也很容易仿造
- "Please don't bully me." - Plus,the artwork is easier to forge.
是,没错,Mickey 你一直这么跟你的同伴这么说的,对吧?
Yeah,that's right,Mickey.You keep telling yourself that,mate,yeah?
谁会想到会干这么个小勾当
Who would have thought it,the great Mickey Bricks taking the easy option.
对,很好 从你这样的寄生虫口里说出来
Yeah,that's good,coming from a parasite like you.
就在靠右边
It's just down here on the right.
真是太棒了,tim肯定会喜欢的
It's perfect.Tim will love it.
- 多谢帮忙 - 没事,很乐意效劳
- Thanks for all your help. - No,it was a pleasure.
那,再见
Bye-bye,then.
3,2,1
Three,two,one.
你待会儿有事吗?
Are you doing anything later?
待会儿有个拍卖,关于连环画艺术的
There's an auction,comic book artwork.
也许你和你侄子会想来?
Maybe you and your nephew would like to come?
- 我们很乐意 - 太好了
- We'd love to. - Great.
很好
Great.
同样栩栩如生的风格 大胆的主色
It's the same energetic style,bold primary colors.
你会在后来Warhol的作品里 找到同样专心致志的东西
The same single-mindedness you later find in Warhol's work.
正是连环画激发了流行艺术运动
The comics inspired the pop-art movement.
我愿不惜一切代价拥有 它的原始的版本
I'd sell my soul to own an original piece.
告诉你个小秘密
I'll let you in on a little secret.
这次拍卖会上我会竞拍 一些原版艺术真迹
I'll be bidding for some original artwork at the auction.
真的?是哪位艺术家?
Really?Which artist?
黑色暴风,连环画界的蒙娜丽沙
Black Storm,the Mona Lisa of comic book artwork.
那我们一起去拍卖会
We could go to the auction together.
好了,我们要2万5英镑
Right,we'll need the 25,000.
- 我跟你一块去 - 别,那可不是个好主意
- I'm coming in with you. - No,that might not be such a good idea.
- 你也知道那些艺术家的样子 - 是啊,你知道,他们非常敏感
- You know what these artists are like. - Yeah,you know,very sensitive.
一说错话,你就侮辱了他
Say the wrong thing and you'll crush him.
别说我们没有警告过你
Don't say we didn't warn you.
要25,000 这幅赝品应该不错
For 25,000,this forgery had better be good.
Danny,你这个帅气的小捣蛋鬼 过来
Danny,you handsome little prick.Come here.
别给我个熊抱(大大的拥抱)
Not the bear hug.
- 嗨,Mickey - 你好吗?
- Hey,Mickey. - How you doing?
嗨,美女
Hello,gorgeous.
Max,我们有点小麻烦 Max,我们真的有要事
Max,we are in a bit of a hurry.Max,we are really in a hurry.
先生们,女士们,这边走
Ladies and gentlemen,walk this way.
他就是这样随性的
He's very up and down.
好了,现在我们来找出哪个是赝品
Okay.Let's play Spot the Forgery.
- 这是胡扯,是不是? - 到底哪一幅?
- Is that the dog's bollocks,or what? - Which one is it?
哦,真是出神入化
Wow,that's brilliant.
- Max,你真是太了不起了 - 简直难辨真伪
- Max,you've excelled yourself. - That is spot on.
你肯定拍卖行认不出来?
Are you sure the auction house won't spot it?
如果他们认出来了 mickey可以拿回那1万5千英镑
The auction house spots it,Mickey can have his 15,000 back.
- 一万五千美元? - 已经打对折了
- Fifteen? - Cheap at half the price.
如果再像这样耍花招 饶不了你
Any more stunts like that,and it won't be the dog's bollocks...
你小心点
that you have to worry about.
- 你俩要不要单独找个房间? - 干什么?
- You two want to get a room? - To do what?
- 我想他吃醋了 - 我可不这么想
- I think he's jealous. - Somehow I doubt it.
那么剩下的一万元呢
Now,what happens to the other 10,000?
那你就好好猜猜吧
Take a wild guess.
干得好,Romeo
Well done,Romeo.
好,接下来干什么?
Okay,what's next?
我要去办些事情
There are some things I need to do.
你干吗不送他把艺术品带回酒吧?
Why don't you take him and the artwork back to the bar?
"他"?我就在这儿,你知道
"Him"?I am here,you know.
我没有艺术品我能干吗?
What can I possibly do without the artwork?
是啊,你来告诉我
Yeah,you tell me.
我来告诉你,你干吗不跟她一块儿?
I tell you what,why don't you stay with her,yeah?
我去取东西
I'll go and pick the stuff up.
好了,看着我 我俩待一块儿,明白没有?
Okay,watch my lips.We stick together.You got it?
不管怎样,我可没心情听 Eddie的抱怨
Anyway,I am really not in the mood for Eddie's whining.
Eddie?
等等.Eddie让你找上我们的
Wait.Eddie put you on to us.
是Eddie?Eddie,Eddie的酒吧.是Eddie?
Eddie?Eddie,Eddie's Bar,Eddie?
Eddie干的,我要宰了他 我会的
Eddie did this.I'm gonna kill him,I will kill him.
算了吧 Eddie只是为了保住面子,跟你一样
Get over it.Eddie's just saving his skin,like you.
我们可跟他不同
He's nothing like us.
天哪,你们对于"小偷间的尊严" 看得有点过头了
God,you really overdo the whole "honor among thieves" business.
我的意思是,要想干有尊严的事情 那就去吧
I mean,want to do the honorable thing,go straight.
好主意,不是吗?真是好 出自你这种警察的嘴里
That's good,isn't it?That's good,coming from a bent cop.
- 我可没有搭过架子 - 那是因为你不能
- I don't pretend there's any honor in it. - That's because you can't.
我去查查有没有我的邮件
I'll just check if there's any mail for me.
你回来晚了,是吧?Max怎么样?
You running a bit late,ain't you?How's Max?
- 赝品行不行? - Ash
- The forgery okay? - Ash.
- 她谁? - Phillips警官
- Who's she? - Detective Inspector Phillips.
- Eddie出卖了我们 - Eddie?谁告诉你的?
- Eddie sold us out. - Eddie?Who told you that?
不可能,她在撒谎.他不会(出卖我们)
No,she's lying.He wouldn't.
我是说,不可能是Eddie
I mean,not Eddie.
这些是不是拍卖行的地图?
Are these the blueprints for the auction house?
就把我当作你沉默的拍档
Think of me as your silent partner.
你打算怎么解决闭路电视的问题?
How are you handling the CCTV?
每个季度都有安全系统来负责
Security system's due for its quarterly service.
包括闭路电视
That includes the CCTV.
我会搞定带子,让带子走 但不会记录下任何东西
I'll rig the tapes so they will be running,they just won't record anything.
这是不是用来掉包艺术品的?
Is that the modified case for switching the artwork?
是的,这个很好用
Yeah.It's good to go.
框架的后面正好跟箱子吻合
The back of the frames match the case.
现在,当Mickey分散大家的注意力
Now,while Mickey distracts everyone...
你就把箱子的另一边推进去
you press the other side of the case against the original...
你加紧快速的把箱子翻过来
you clip it on,you flip the case over...
赝品出来了,然后你就离开
the forgery releases,and off you go.
好的,小菜一碟
Yeah,piece of cake.
小菜一碟
Piece of cake.
保安系统就在你脚下
You will have security down on you like a ton of bricks.
听着,也许该由你来做
Listen,maybe you should do it.
好了,你们都泼我冷水 啊?我来,行吧?我能搞定的
Yeah,does everyone want to chill out,okay?I'll do it,okay?I'm going to do it.
- 你们管好你们自己 - 没人会为我担心的
- You just look after your end. - No one's worried about my end.
Mickey,也许你该给自己找个好姑娘 那所有都会改变的
Mickey,maybe you should find yourself a nice girl and all that will change.
给我的时间,行吧,Mickey?
Been a while,has it,Mickey?
是,我能说什么?我会慎重选择的
Yeah,what can I say?I'm very choosy.
你去下拍卖行
You need to get down to the auction house.
是的,我搞定了他们的闭路电视 我就打电话给你
Yeah.I will call when I've rigged the CCTV.
那之前,你最好别去
You don't want to set foot in there before then.
好好练习一下,Danny
Keep practicing,Danny.
下次.直接上,没问题的 这个不是问题
Next time.Go straight on,all right.It's not a problem.
那,分散了注意力
And distraction.
正如我所说的,Mickey,这个小意思
Like I said,Mickey,it is a piece of cake.
好吧,那我们去吧
Okay,we got to go.
哦,等等,稍稍奖励一下 应该不会误事的
Yeah,hang on a minute,a little bit of appreciation for that wouldn't go amiss.
你搞定了,我给你买个冰激凌
You pull this off,I'll give you an ice cream.
你在后面行吧,Mickey?够不够地方搁你的小腿?
You all right in the back,Mickey?Got enough room for your little legs?
- 右转 - 向右,你疯啦?应该直走
- Take the next right. - Right.You mad?It's straight on.
右转可以避免单行道 右转
Turning right avoids the one-way system.Take a right.
别听他的,亲爱的,直走
Don't listen to him,love,straight on.
- 老实说,我们现在哪里? - Manor路上
- Actually,where are we? - Manor Road.
对,哦,没错.右转
Right,yeah,it is right.Take the next right.
Danny,闭嘴
Danny,shut up.
- 我们干吗停下来? - 两分钟
- Why are we stopping? - I'll be two minutes.
- 干吗? - 我们来不及了
- Doing what? - We don't have time for this.
好吧,那这么办
Okay,here's the deal.
安全起见我们各自拿着一件艺术品
We keep one set of artwork each as security.
- 你在开玩笑? - 干吗不让我们跟你一快?
- Are you having a laugh? - Why don't we just come with you?
你们在这里等着 我来拿真品
You wait here.I will take the genuine piece.
如你所说,我们没有时间搞这个
Like you said,we don't have time for this.
好了,谢谢你
Great,thank you.
哪里也别想去,啊?
Weren't planning on going anywhere,were you?
不,我从来没有过这个想法
No,the thought hadn't even crossed my mind.
有没有认跟你说过你有点妄想症?
Has anyone ever told you you're paranoid?
有,我还要你的电话
Yep,I will take your phones,too...
以防你们在我背后搞小动作
just in case you were tempted to make any arrangements behind my back.
我会给你的,但我的意思是说
I would give it,but I mean,
我奶奶说过今天要打电话给我,她非常孤单
me Nan said she might call today.She gets very Ionely.
哦,如果奶奶打来了
Yeah,if me Nan calls...
就跟她说明天我会去看她
just tell her I'll come and see her tomorrow.
你拿到你要的东西了吗?
Did you get what you needed?
画还在,Danny
It's still there,Danny.
那么,你男朋友是不是在这里工作?
So,your boyfriend work round here,does he?
你有没有男朋友?没有?
You got a boyfriend?No?
怎么,你脾气不好?
What,you're more of a cat person?
嘿,停下里
Hey,stop them !
把我们的包还给我们,小偷!
Give our bag back,pricks!
嘿,停车!
Hey,stop that car!
这下好了
Great.
- 你怎么追的啊? - 好啊,我就是这么追的
- You call that running? - Yes,I call that running.
- 那你去哪里了? - 就在你后面
- Where were you? - Right behind you.
- 如果我知道你会减速 - 听着,这是我的错
- lf I knew you were going to slow down... - Look,it's not my fault.
- 这可不是我的错 - 当然是你的错
- Do not make this my fault. - It is your fault!
你让个白痴拿了箱子 这还我的错?
You let some idiot take the case and it's my fault?
- 闭嘴! - 我是跟着你过来的
- Shut up! - I've had it up to here with you.
- 你老是自做主张 - 我们现在去把它找出来
- Always got to have things your own way. - Let's sort it out now!
闭嘴,Danny,上车!
Shut up,Danny,and get in the car!
哦,这算什么意思?
Is that supposed to mean something?
我们刚刚搞砸了,好吗?那是真品
We just got screwed,all right?That was the real artwork.
我们真的要这么千方百计 要我打电话给拍卖行
Do we really have to go through the whole me phoning the auction house...
让我在最后一刻制止我?我想如果你们想的话,我可以这么做
you stopping me at the last minute thing?I mean,we can if you like.
跟你说吧,她不会这么做的
Told you she wouldn't go for it.
我想你没有更好的主意了
I didn't see you coming up with any better ideas.
你到底怎么做到的?
When exactly did you arrange it?
我去看邮件的时候 在旅馆留了张便条给Ash
I left a note for Ash at the hotel,when I checked my mail.
你不能因此怪我们吧?
You can't blame us for trying,can you?
哦,好吧,如果你们不这么急着摆脱我 我想我也不会这么急
Yeah,well,I'd probably be more worried if you weren't trying to ditch me,I suppose.
换给你
Here you go.
他把艺术品拿哪里了?
Where's he taking the artwork?
你真的以为我们不知道?
Did you really think we wouldn't find out?
什么?你很抱歉?哦,这太迟了,不是吗?
What's that?You're sorry?Well it's too late,son,isn't it?
她买了没有?
Did she buy it?
放了他
Let him go.
我说了,放他走
I said,let him go.
Mickey,我很抱歉 是她威胁我
Mickey,I'm sorry.She was trying to blackmail me.
她弄了假钞 她说我会进监狱
She planted some counterfeit money.She told me I was going to prison.
当我们来跟你算帐的时候 你会希望如此的
You'll wish you had when we get through with you.
Mickey,求求你.我们认识多久了?
Mickey,please.How long have we known each other?
我别无选择
I didn't have any choice.
Danny?
上帝,Eddie,你让我有揍你的冲动
Jesus,Eddie,you're making me want to kick you.
我想我们还要去拍卖会
I believe we have an auction to go to.
他怎么办?
What about him?
我拿到我的钱,这就是你的事
What you do after I get my money,that's your business.
我们有过协议
We had a deal.
- 你不能这样! - 待会见,Eddie.
- You can't do this! - Later,Eddie.
我不小心滑了下
I slipped.
- 一点历史 - 它在哪儿?
- A slice of history. - And where is it?
今天下午晚点会到
It's not arriving till later this afternoon.
我已经迫不及待要看一眼了
I didn't expect to get another shot at it so soon.
- 你料到这么多的竞争了吗? - 都是些怪人
- Are you expecting much competition? - Only the geek.
Neil Davis.连环画收藏家
Neil Davis.Comic book collector.
纯粹是处于角色的神秘
Thinks it's all about the mythology of the characters.
与艺术意义完全无关
No appreciation of the artistic significance.
我想他甚至与无法拼出Lichtenstein
I mean he couldn't even spell Lichtenstein.
那一旦他得到了这么件真品 那将是巨大的悲哀
Then it would be a tragedy if he acquired such an important piece.
我会确保他不会得逞
I will just have to make sure that he doesn't.
嗨,你来了
Hi.You made it.
给你
Here.
- 你没必要这样 - 哦,我心甘情愿
- You didn't have to do that. - Yeah,I wanted to.
这位是谁啊?
And who's this?
这是鸟?飞机?不,这是
Is it a bird?Is it a plane?No,it's....
是Tim.跟Neil打个招呼,Tim
This is Tim.Say hello to Neil,Tim.
他非常喜欢自己的装扮 不肯脱下来
He absolutely loves his costume.Wouldn't take it off.
我希望我也有这么套行头
I wish I'd got one.
也许下一次?
Maybe some other time?
- 我们进去吧? - 好的
- Shall we go in? - Yeah.
他非常兴奋
He's really excited.
好吧,他要花些时间 那我们找个地方坐坐
Right,he'll be a while.So let's take the weight off.
那我们现在在看的是什么?
So,what is it we are looking at?
黑色风暴原版的封面,出品的第一版
The original artwork for the cover of Black Storm,Issue One,when it arrives.
所以我可以把它当作是个大买卖?
And I take it this is a big deal?
是的
Yeah.
他是第一个真正意义上的超级英雄 有着巨大的影响力
He was one of the very first superheroes.Massively influential.
为我们所知的后来的连环画建立了雏形
Shaped the future of comics as we know them.
- 噢,了不起  - 我打算竞拍它
- Wow. - I'm bidding for it.
那人是谁?
And who's that?
Gideon Sturock,竞争对手
Gideon Sturock.The competition.
看上去是个自命不凡的傻子
Looks like a pretentious little prat to me.
他自称是艺术收藏家
He calls himself an art collector.
他根本不顾画中的人物或神话
He doesn't care about the characters or the mythology.
对他来说,这不过是又一个战利品
It's just another trophy to him.
那我希望你别让他得逞
I hope you are not going to let him buy it,then?
我会尽我所能的
Not if I can help it.
- 那个怪人 - 真的吗?
- The geek. - Really?
跟他在一起的迷人女士是谁?
Who's that rather attractive young woman with him?
如果她和这么个没用的人在一起 大概是个妓女
If she's with a loser like that,probably a hooker.
我非常期待看你打败他时 他脸上的表情
I'm very much going to enjoy seeing the look on his face when you outbid him.
干得好,Ash
Good work,Ash.
闭路电视搞定了,到我们了
CCTV's rigged.We're on.
你俩先走,行吧?
You two go ahead,all right?
这有关系吗?
Is there a problem?
你们将要犯罪 而显然,我不想被连累
You are about to commit a crime.Obviously I can't be associated with that.
好吧
Okay.
你自己去喝杯茶,行吧 还有甜圈,怎么样?
Get yourself a nice a cup of tea,yeah?Sticky bun,all right?
Danny,我就在你后面 现在,你别跟我说话
Danny,I will be right behind you.Now,you don't talk to me...
你不知道我 不认识我
you don't acknowledge me,you don't know me...
但你要在我的视野范围内 听清楚了没有?
but you stay in sight.Clear?
几点开始,3:30?好的,行不行?
What time does it start,3:30?Okay,is that any good?
叫Colossal
Colossal.
- 他在那儿干吗? - 他妈我怎么会知道?
- What's he doing here? - How the hell am I supposed to know?
- 怎么回事? - 计划大师搞砸了
- What is going on? - Master planner here screwed up.
拍卖行通常会有一个专家
The auction house usually have an expert...
进来对艺术品进行鉴定
come in and authenticate the artwork...
- 在进行拍卖之前 - 好,你知道的
- before they put it up for auction. - Yeah,you knew that.
是,我是知道,但不是以前那个
Yes,I did,but this is not their usual guy.
他们找来的这个6个月前 把我们哄了出去
The guy they've brought in rumbled us six months ago...
我们想卖幅Andy Warhol画作的赝品
when we tried to sell a forged Andy Warhol print.
是的,我们拿着一大堆垃圾邮件
Yeah,we had these tins of Spam.
我们让他们忙坏了 他们很有意思
We'd had them all stacked up.They were cute.
我们不能在他在场的情况 下拍卖这件艺术品
We cannot put the artwork up for auction with him there.
我们必须要推迟
We are going to have to postpone.
除了要我做出格的事情,这倒方便了
Just till I'm out of the way.Deeply convenient.
你要不要我们走出去 向你证明这一切?
Would you like us to step outside and prove it to you?
好吧,那Ash怎么办?是的
All right,what about Ash?Yeah.
我们可以让他先装下去,他能做到的
We will get him all,you know,disguised,he can do it.
不行,他已经为闭路电视服务过了
No,he's been servicing their CCTV.
- 那我们要另外找人 - Danny,没有时间了,对不起
- We'll have to get someone else,then. - Danny,there is no time.Sorry.
- 我是说放弃这个 - 不行,我们不可能再弄次闭路电视的
- I'm calling it off. - No,we can't rig the CCTV a second time.
买家们已经准备好了,每个人都 各就各位了.我们必须上
Buyers are ready.Everybody's in place.Got to go now.
- 我可以做 - 哦,是的,我可不这么想
- I could do it. - Yeah,right.I don't think so.
是的,她可以做么
Yeah.She can do it.
然后看着她时候带着钱消失
And watch her disappear with the money afterwards.
你疯了?
Are you out of your mind?
我们还换的是吧?我们还有原迹
We still make the switch.Yeah?We still got the original.
我是说,那也能行
I mean,that could work.
我想你该试着相信我
I guess you're gonna have to trust me.
好吧,拍卖会再等一位Henshaw先生
All right,the auction house are expecting a Mr.Henshaw.
我打电话告诉他们我的助理 代我来送艺术品
I'll call and tell them that my PA will be delivering the artwork instead of me.
你换之前在大厅等我回来,没问题吧?
Wait until I am back in the foyer before you make the switch,all right?
当你上的时候,我可不想离你这么近
I don't want to be anywhere near you when you do it.
Williams先生,请
Mr.Williams,please.
嗨,我是Henshaw先生的助手
Hello,I'm Mr.Henshaw's PA.
我想你在等我
I think you are expecting me.
那么,我得知你的专家今天不在吗?
So,I understand your own expert isn't in today?
Paul?不,他今天早上打电话说病了
Paul?No,he called in sick this morning.
我们不得不最后时刻请来David
We had to get David in here at the last minute.
- 这是真品 - 今天展上最好的
- It's authentic. - Best get this on display.
我知道Henshaw先生要赶飞机 所以我会开张银行汇款给你
I know Mr.Henshaw has a plane to catch,so I will issue you with a banker's draft...
- 一卖出就给你 - 好的,谢谢
- immediately after the sale. - Great.Thank you.
我有感觉,你将非常失望
Something tells me you are going to be horribly disappointed.
我们走着瞧,不是吗?
We'll just have to see about that,won't we?
她真漂亮
Pretty girl.
她开价多少?
How much does she charge?
好了
Yeah.
该我们上了
We're on.
妈妈!
Mama !
孩子,谁要啊?
Kids.Who'd have them?
我有四个
I've got four.
很好,我喜欢孩子 他们跟他们母亲一样漂亮吗?
Great,I love them.They as good-looking as their mom?
女士们,先生们,请各位就座
Ladies and gentlemen,if you could please take your seats...
我们今天的拍卖会马上就要开始了
we will get today's auction underway.
我们先从2周前在此被买走的一幅开始
We start with the resale of a piece that was purchased two weeks ago...
进行第二次拍卖
at this very auction house.
拍卖物一:黑色风暴的原作封面
Lot Number One is the original artwork...
第一版
for the cover of Black Storm,Issue One.
由Leonard Wright做于1934年 这是个里程碑式的作品
Drawn in 1934 by Leonard Wright,it's a landmark piece...
具有文化性和艺术性
both culturally and artistically.
起价是6万英镑
I'll open the bidding at just 60,000.
6万.6万5
Sixty.Sixty-five.
7万
Seventy.
7万5
Seventy-five.
8万,8万英镑
Eighty.At 80,000.
8万5
Eighty-five.
9万
Ninety.
9万5
Ninety-five.
At ninety-five.
10万
One hundred.
10万英镑?
At 100,000.
10万5千
One-five.
11万
One-ten.
11万5千
One-fifteen.
后悔是非常可悲的一件事情
Regret is a terrible thing.
12万
One-twenty.
12万英镑
At 120,000.
有没有更高的价?
Any more bids?
12万一次
Going once.
2次
Going twice.
别出价
Don't bid.
成交!
Sold!
减去代理费,这是10万8千美元
Minus our commission,that's 108,000.
你到手了?
Did you get it?
- 你个小美人 - 我去兑现,然后给你一半
- You little beauty. - I will cash it and give you your half.
你知道吗?那对我不管用
You know what?That doesn't really work for me.
什么?
Excuse me?
她说的跟我认为她说的一样的吗?
Did she just say what I think she said?
诈骗,欺骗,攻击一个酒吧男侍
Fraud,deception,assaulting a bartender.
我说你们不是已经得到一份不错 的犯案记录了,不是吗?
I mean you two have racked up quite a charge sheet,haven't you?
别忘了,你跟我们是一路的
Don't forget you've been with us every step of the way.
我吗?
Me?
我是一个卧底警察
I am an undercover police officer.
当然,我们是一伙的
Of course I've been with you every step of the way.
我是说,有其他证据吗?
I mean,how else would I obtain evidence?
你干吗不做个好姑娘呢?
Why don't you just be a good little girl,yeah?
交接吧?
Hand it over?
规矩点,Danny
Play nice,Danny.
现在,跟之前一样
Now,same deal as before.
我拿钱,要么你们进监狱,怎么样?
I keep the money or you go to prison.What's it to be?
我告诉你吧,你们保留原作,当作费用
I tell you what,you keep the original artwork,cover expenses.
我们需不需要表示感谢?
Are we supposed to be grateful?
我根本不在乎你干什么
I really don't care what you are.
现在我要走出那扇门 而你们当作不知道
Now I am going to walk out that door,you are going to leave it...
10分钟,你们就自由了
ten minutes,then you're free to go.
什么,你真以为会这样?
What,and you really think that's going to happen?
相信我,Danny,你一点都 不适合穿监狱服,伙计
Trust me,Danny,you really wouldn't suit prison overalls,mate.
我吗?我穿什么都好看
Me?I look good in anything.
你,我倒要看看了
You,I will see around.
这是个非常非常不明智的举动
That's a very,very bad move.
太伟大了
Simply magnificent.
不好意思
Excuse me.
- 这个太古怪了 - 什么?
- That's rather odd. - What's that?
黑色暴风带着个印章戒指 我记得以前好像没有
Black Storm's wearing a signet ring.I don't recall seeing that before.
Max,我们需要一份拷贝 还有另外一份带有瑕疵的拷贝
Max,we need one identical copy and then another copy with a small flaw.
瑕疵?
A flaw?
你们心里怎么想的?
What sort of thing did you have in mind?
哦,我的天哪
Oh,my God.
- 等等,你怎么回事,嗨? - 对不起
- Wait a minute,where are you,hello? - Sorry.
- 哦,算了 - 对不起
- Right.Okay. - Sorry.
Jackson小姐
Miss Jackson.
你送来拍卖的作品事实上是赝品
It appears that the artwork you put up for sale is,in fact,a forgery.
警察在赶来的路上
The police are on their way.
好吧,我是Phillips警官 我在执行卧底的任务
Right.D.I.Phillips.I am working undercover.
嫌疑犯还在里面,对吧?
The suspects are still inside,all right?
我们以前也和警方合作过 他们都会通知我们
We've worked with the police before.They've always notified us in the past.
- 出于手续原因,我们不能 - 我们?你的支援呢?
- We couldn't,for operational reasons. - We?Where's your backup?
今天就我一个
I'm working on my own today.
我们为什么不进去谈?
Why don't we discuss this inside?
你们干什么?我是警察
What are you doing?I am a police officer.
好样的,大个子,啊?放开我!
Feel good,big man,does it?Get your hands off me!
Cole警官,Martin探员
D.I.Cole,this is D.S.Martin.
在过去几个月里,我打入这群人内部
I've been working the inside with this crew for the last couple of months.
告诉我们,你为什么要卖这件艺术品
Tell us why you put the artwork up for sale.
艺术专家认识他们
The art expert knew them.
这是让他们拿着它进来的唯一的办法
It was the only way I could get them to go through with it.
听着,他们的名字是 请记住这个,行吗
Look,their names are,just remember this,all right...
Michael Stone,Danny Blue,和Ash Morgan.去查Mickey的案底
Michael Stone,Danny Blue,and Ash Morgan.Check Mickey's record.
好了,她的身份没错,对不起
Okay.She checks out.Sorry.
谢谢你们,他们溜了 而我也暴露了身份
Thanks to you,they've got away,and my cover's blown.
我又怎么会知道?
How was I to know?
身份证和艺术品都有可能是假的
The ID and artwork could've both been forgeries.
那么,摄像头在哪里?
So,what's the scam?
听着,他们在展品展出的时候 把真的和假的掉了包
Look,they switched the authentic artwork for a forgery while it was on display.
- 我知道,那这里的闭路电视呢? - 不管用的
- I take it you have CCTV here? - Won't help.
Ash Morgan曾是个工程师
Ash Morgan posed as an engineer.
他改装过了闭路电视 所以它什么也不会录下
He rigged the CCTV,so it recorded absolutely nothing.
今天,我们没有请过工程师
We haven't had an engineer here today.
我个人授权所有的维修 如果我们有,我会知道的
I personally authorize all maintenance.I would've known if we had.
我们为什么不去看一看?
Why don't we take a look at it?
正如我所说的,它工作正常
Like I said,it's working perfectly.
这个男人Ash并没有离开拍卖行
This guy Ash didn't leave the auction room.
听着,他准备了个假身份证 我是说,我明明看见了
Look,he prepared a fake ID.I mean I saw it,so....
即使有了假身份证
Even with a fake ID...
他在闭路系统附近什么也干不了
there is no way he would've got anywhere near the CCTV system.
就这里,这就是他们 Mickey,那个黑人小子
There you go.That's them.Mickey,the black guy.
他用了个Henshaw的假名字
He was using the name Henshaw.
他从你哪里买到了真品,2个星期前
He bought the artwork from you,like,about two weeks ago.
那不是Henshaw先生 Henshaw先生是白人
That's not Mr.Henshaw.Mr.Henshaw's white.
11美元
One-ten.
也不是另外一个
It's not the other guy,either.
那儿,现在,我跟着他们,对吧
There,now,I follow them,okay.
到楼梯间的摄像头
Go to the camera in the stairwell.
楼梯间没有摄像头
There are no cameras in the stairwell.
如果闭路电视正常 你会看到他们换画
If the CCTV's working,you will see them switch the artwork.
没问题,他们并没有走近 黑色暴风连环画
Nope,they didn't go anywhere near the Black Storm artwork.
等等,你知道的,他们肯定会的
Wait,you know,they must have.
我能看到你在边上
I can see you near it.
- 现在怎么了? - 没什么
- What's happening now? - That's nothing.
有个孩子放了他的气球
Some kid let go of his balloons.
那么我们唯一失去图像的时候 是你站在它边上
So the only time we lose sight of the artwork,you're standing right next to it.
- 盒子里是什么? - 没什么,是空的
- What's in the case? - Nothing.It was empty.
从我为他们送了画开始我就拿着它
I still had it from when I delivered the artwork for them.
那么,我听说你的专家今天没来
So,I understand your own expert isn't in today.
Paul?不,他今天早上打电话来请了病假
Paul?No,he called in sick this morning.
好吧,在我检查的时候 我要你把热帽打开
Okay,I need you to turn the hot tap on in the bathroom while I check it.
对不起,伙计
Sorry,pal.
现在箱子在哪里?
Where's the case now?
我把它还给Mickey和Danny
I gave it back to Mickey and Danny.
当我们遗失画的时候Mickey 和Danny在哪里?
Where were Mickey and Danny when we lost the picture?
在大厅,没有靠近展品黑色风暴
In the foyer,nowhere near the Black Storm artwork.
你还拿着那张银行汇票,是不是?
You do still have the banker's draft,don't you?
是的,当然
Yeah,of course.
那个女人,和带气球的孩子
The woman and the kid with the balloons.
那么,这是什么?也许我们该去查查
So,what's this?Maybe we should check this out.
我还有其他证据
I've got other evidence.
听着,他们在骗一个地产商 这里
Listen,they were running a con on some estate agent.Here you go.
Richard Shaw,对吧?这就是他们骗的那个人
Richard Shaw,all right?That's the guy they were conning.
他可以完全解释我的话
He will totally back up my story.
你做不做傻瓜?这是2万5千镑
You'd have to be an idiot not to.25,000.
Richard Shaw地产商?
Richard Shaw.Estate agent?
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
听着,我可以带你们去 那个伪造的工作室
Look,I can take you to the forger's studio.
好吧,让我们来找出赝品
Okay.Let's play Spot the Forgery.
我告诉你们了,他们把钥匙塞给我的
I told you,they planted the key on me.
那为什么保险箱是以你的名字登记的?
How come the safe deposit box is registered in your name?
拍卖行的地图?
Blueprints for the auction house.
关于黑色风暴的调查
Research on Black Storm.
而这里有1万英镑
And there's got to be 10,000 here.
剩下的一万呢?
What happens to the other 10,000?
好好猜猜吧
Take a wild guess.
他们把我开到了这里
They steered me here.
但这是你的保险箱 是你登记的
But it's your safe deposit box.It's registered to you.
是的,但他们知道我会在 去的路上看保险箱
Yeah,but they knew I'd see the safe depository when we drove past.
- 老实说,我们在哪里? - Manor路
- Actually,where are we? - Manor Road.
哦,对,没错,右转
Right,yeah,it is right.Take the next right.
他们早知道我有个保险箱在这里
They must have known I had a box here.
那他们怎么拿到你保险箱里的东西呢?
And how would they get inside your safe deposit box?
这个假的
It's counterfeit.
那这是什么?
What's this,then?
Eddie
Eddie.
她就是那个两面派警察
She's this bent D.I.
她抓了Billy和他手下 到这儿来赌博,你知道
She caught Billy and his crew gambling down here,you know...
他们玩纸牌
they were playing poker.
她要1万英镑,否则我就得丢执照
She wants 10,000,or I lose me license.
我可能一无所有,Mick
And I could lose everything,Mick.
- 你和我想得一样吗? - 是的
- Are you thinking what I am thinking? - Yup.
她漂亮吗?
Is she fit?
- 好吧,我可以带你们去他们的旅馆 - 住宾馆并没有违法
- Okay,I can take you to their hotel. - It's not illegal to stay in a hotel.
- 是的,但我们可以搞张搜查令 - 出于什么理由?
- Yeah,but we can get a search warrant. - On what grounds?
Mickey和Danny并没有来卖画 是你卖的
Mickey and Danny didn't put the artwork up for sale,you did.
是你拿了银行支票
You collected the banker's draft.
就我们所知,他们也没有调包画 而你
As far as we can tell,they didn't switch the artwork,either,whereas you....
那是闭路电视的镜头,这是证据
There's CCTV footage,witnesses.
听着,所有这一切,拍品
Look,all this.Everything,the lot,okay?
都是Mickey和Danny的
It's all Mickey and Danny.
没有任何证据表明,你跟他们说过话
There's no evidence you even spoke to them.
也没有所谓的伪造者Max 没有Richard Shaw
There's no Max the Forger.There's no Richard Shaw.
Mickey和Danny没有做出 任何违法的事情
This Mickey and Danny don't appear to have done anything illegal.
不管怎么说,至少今天没有
At least not today,anyway.
- 而这些从哪儿来的? - 他们设计的
- Where did all this come from? - They planted it.
- 是他们算计了我 - 你能证明吗?
- They are setting me up. - Can you prove it?
我没有选择的余地,对不起
I don't have any choice.I'm sorry.
Samantha Phillips,我怀疑你 涉嫌偷窃,诈骗,拘捕你
Samantha Phillips.I am arresting you on suspicion of theft,fraud,and deception.
你可以保持沉默
You do not have to say anything...
但这将影响你的辩护 如果你对所提问的只字不提
but it may harm your defense if you do not mention when questioned...
这都将会是你的成堂证供
something which you later rely on in court.
看吧,桌上的卡片
Come on,cards on the table.
你会不会对她粗暴点?
Would you have a little knock-about with her?
正如所说的,Danny,我很挑剔的
Like I said,Danny,I'm very choosy.
是的,但是挑剔也没什么不好
Yeah,but choosy ain't getting you nowhere.
尤其当她把警棍拿出来对着我的时候
When she got that truncheon out,did it for me.
女人是氪(你克星)
Women are your kryptonite.
你在干吗,你那是在干什么?旅游还是什么?
What are you on about,what are you on?Are you tripping or something?
我是他们的氪 Albert,我,听着
I'm their kryptonite.Albert,I....Listen.
- 女人对我无法抗拒 - 是的,接着做梦吧
- Women are powerless to resist me. - Yeah,dream on.
- 好的,我来载你们 - 不,我来开
- Right,I'll drive you. - No,I'm driving.
让我来开
Let me drive.
你能帮我开下门吗?
Would you open the door for me,please?
- 要让我们干所有的事情,是不是? - 谢谢
- Want us to do everything,yeah? - Thank you.
我不想开车,行了吧?所以我骗了你,我赢了
I didn't want to drive,okay?So I tricked you,so I won.
你开,我不开.算了吧
You drive,I am not driving.Forget it.
等等,爸爸
But,Dad.
- 十分荣幸 - 拿着吧,你的第一份奖金
- Always a pleasure. - Here you go,your first score.
- 就这些? - 闭嘴
- Is that all? - Shut up.
- 他学得很快 - 伙计们,待会见
- He's learning fast. - I'll see you around,guys.
- 谢谢 - 很高兴跟你合作
- Thank you. - Nice working with you.
走吧,我们回家去
Come on,let's get you home.
- Eddie,怎么了? - 我滑了一跤
- Eddie,what happened? - I slipped.
是的,在你来酒吧前我没时间用填充物
Yeah,I didn't have time to fit the padding before you got to the bar.
哦,我们什么也不能说,对吧?
Yeah,I couldn't exactly say anything,could I?
欺骗是个很危险的游戏,Eddie
Grifting's a dangerous game,Eddie.
但从好的一面来看
But look on the bright side...
至少Phillips警官 不会再打扰你了
at least D.I.Phillips won't be bothering you anymore.
是得,这下好了,谢谢,伙计们
Yeah,nice one.Thanks,fellas.
那我呢就去兑现了来自拍卖行的汇款
So,I cashed the banker's draft we got from the auction house.
钱在这里,8万英镑
The money's in here,along with the 80,000...
Neil很高兴能买下原稿
that Neil very happily paid for the original.
危险,但是诱人
Dangerous,but lucrative.
这是不是意味着你们能够结帐了?
So does this mean you lot are going to settle your tab?
- Eddie. - 有意思
- Eddie. - Charming.
- 你的感激之情呢? - 也不谢谢
- Where's the gratitude? - No appreciation.
你想想我们干吗这么烦
Makes you wonder why we bother.
好吧,这里
All right,then,here.
好了,我搞定了
Okay then,I'd better be off.
等等
Hold on.
你盛装打扮要去哪里?
Where are you going all dressed up?
我不认为这与你有关,Danny
I don't think that's,any of your business,Danny.
- 她要去约会 约会? - 跟谁?
- She's got a date. - A date?Who with?
我想这跟你也没有关系
I don't think that's any of your business,either.
- Neil. - Neil,是Neil?
- Neil. - Neil.Neil?
你要跟个连环画怪胎约会
You are going out with some specky comic-book geek,when...
而弃像我这样英俊,善良,幽默 敏锐和有创造性的男人
a beautiful,friendly,funny,sensitive,creative guy...
在一边?
like me doesn't even get a look in?
就是这样,不是吗,Danny?
Looks that way.Doesn't it,Danny?
好了,伙计们,别等太晚
Okay,guys,don't wait up.
打牌,绅士们?
Cards,gentlemen?
打牌?对,好主意
Cards?Yeah,brilliant.
我简直无法抑制我的激动
I can hardly handle the excitement.
什么?
What?
我们说好,一把10块?
Shall we say,a tenner a hand?
- 不,不行 - Eddie,来吧
- No.No way. - Eddie,come on.
随便玩玩
Just a bit of fun.
另外,你现在也是我们的一员了
Besides,you're one of the crew now.
那么,Eddie,你什么牌?
So,Eddie,what do you got?
以为我会告诉你?
Like I'd tell you lot.